Hello everyone! I'm
Hello các bạn ơi bạn đế sử Bá nhá ch Bá
so happy to be here! Are you happy too? So happy!
vui lắm Các bạn có thấy vui không vui bá
So happy! Oh
vui C kỳ vui ô
yeah! In the middle of the night, under the moonlight,
yeah tâ C trong sắc giữa đêm tră ng chưa
we're rolling around with so many things, we're so happy, are
ta lăn tiế với bao m bế ch ta lưu lế vui
n't we? Always reading together, or maybe we'll connect with each
không luôn về đọc cùng nhau hay Né
other, so much love.
đ cù nhau kết nỗi yêu thương qu th Mùa
Every summer, let's sing together,
Hè nào cùng nhau hay hát
a connection of all directions. The love
vang một kết nối muôn Phương K th tình
that parents know, keep it to yourselves. Today
mà bố vẹ ai cũng biết giử ba rồi Hôm nay
I think I'll be able to send so many things,
em nghĩ mình sẽ gử được bao nhiêu cái
like 100,
nh 100
I have to wash dishes for my parents, but when
w m có giả bát cho bố mẹ không có nhưng
I get home I have a few dishes already, but when I get
mà về nhà có máy giờ bát r nhưng mà về
home I have a few dishes already, Mom and Dad! I'm going to wash
nhà có máy giờ bát r bố mẹ ơi C bi rửa
dishes, oh what? This is the first time I've
bát rồi ố gì á Đây là lần đầu tiên em
washed dishes and I feel very happy, but my
rửa bát và em thấy rất vui mà rừa hơi
shirt is a little wet. Do I have anything to say to my parents?
ướt áo em có lời gì muốn nói với bố mẹ
No. Next time I'll wash dishes
không có ạ Lần sau thì con sẽ dựa bát
for my
cho bố
parents. Thank you, Mom and Dad, for letting me go to the
mẹ cảm ơn bố mẹ vì đã cho em đi khóa tu
Ba Vang retreat. I think this retreat is very
chố Ba Vàng em thấy là cái khóa này rất
meaningful. Mom and Dad, I've made Ken a new guy.
là ý nĩa bố mẹ ơi con làm Ken được môi
Here he is, Mom and Dad, don't worry.
chư Đây rồi bố mẹ không cần lo đâu ạ Cảm
Thank you, Dad.  Mom helped me register for this course and I'm
ơn bố mẹ đã giúp con đăng ký kháa tu này
so happy! I will grow up
con cảm thấy rất vui ạ Con sẽ lớn khôn
and help my parents. Mom and Dad, we
và sẽ giúp đỡ ba mẹ bố mẹ ơi chúng con
already know how to play
đã biết r bắt
[music]
[âm nhạc]
[Applause]
[Vỗ tay]